cartradeindia.com 2013-12-05

# Privacy Policy | CarTrade.com

## _COMPANY PRIVACY POLICY AND OPT-OUT_    (Effective from 22nd August, 2013)

During your use of CarTrade.com, we will collect certain information about you (in the following, 'You' refers to any visitor using the website CarTrade.com, in general or in the use of specific functions). We highly value your privacy and the Privacy Policy that follows explains exactly what data we collect and how it will be used.

_**Use of Site Browsing History**_

By using CarTrade.com, You consent to the collection, storage, and use of your browsing history on this website. We share this information with trusted 3rd parties that use it to show your marketing communications of interest. While no Personally Identifiable Information is shared, we respect your right to privacy and hence provide this transparent disclosure. In addition, selected 3rd parties also provide You the right to opt out. To opt out from all 3rd parties that make use of Adobe technology, please click on the link below and select the appropriate option on the destination page.

Click [here](http://www.adobe.com/in/privacy/opt-out.html?button=Opt-Out) to opt out of Adobe programmes.

_**Opt Out Page**_

You can also opt out of several similar programs by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative gateway opt-out site. In addition, You may also setup your browser software to reject 3rd party cookies.

Click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for the Network Advertising opt-out site.

_**Visitor Profiling**_

During your visit, our system will register various details about your usage, including but not limited to the duration of your stay, your geographical location and the pages You visit on our site. This is done through the use of amongst others cookies.

As part of your usage of CarTrade.com You may provide your personal details such as name, phone number and email address. These details may be used by CarTrade.com and/or provided to third parties in order to provide and/or administer our services, to help us understand the user behavior, to monitor website performance, optimize ads and measure advertising performance.

_**Mailing List** _

While providing your email address to CarTrade, either during the sale of a vehicle, while contacting a buyer, applying for a new car price, or via subscribing to the newsletter form on news pages or any other relevant form, You agree to be included in our mailing list. Our mailing list is an opt-in mailing list, and You can unsubscribe by using the relevant link in the email. Your mail address will not be provided to any outside party.

_**Security** _

All your personal data are stored on CarTrade's servers. They have been secured, both physically and electronically, and cannot be accessed by any third party. We value your security highly and we do make best efforts to keep your data safe.

_**Third Party Links** _

CarTrade provides links to other third parties. While we encourage our partners to use privacy policies, we cannot be held responsible for their use or non-use of such policies.

_**Agreement** _

By use of CarTrade.com You agree that You are aware of our Privacy Policy and your approval of the same. You further understand that this policy may be altered in due course. Your continued use of this website following the effective date of any such amendment shall be deemed to constitute your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended. By visiting CarTrade.com, You agree that your visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy. 

_**Information Collected About You and your Computer**_

We may collect "Non-Personal Information"- information that cannot be used to identify You - via Cookies, even if You have not registered with or provided any Personal Information to CarTrade.com.

Our webserver automatically collects and may store limited information about your computer configuration when You visit our website, including the type of browser software You use, the operating system You are running, the resolution of your computer monitor, and your IP address. We shall use IP address information for systems administration (including fraud detection and prevention) and troubleshooting purposes. We may also collect information about the website You were visiting before You came to our website and the website You visit after You leave our website.

_**What Choices Do I Have?**_

Most browser software can be set to reject Cookies, and You can opt out of Cookies for several Ad Servers by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative gateway opt-out site.

_**Changes To This Privacy Policy**_

If we need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on this website together with an updated reference to its effective date to reflect the date of the amendment. Your continued use of this website following the effective date of any such amendment shall be deemed to constitute your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended. By visiting CarTrade.com, You agree that your visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy.

_**How Information Collected About You Is Used?**_

By registering yourself at CarTrade.com you authorize us & both our current and future associate partners (including but not limited to financial partners such as but not only ICICI Bank and several automotive partners) to communicate with you via SMS, Email, Phone or any other means to offer you their services, imparting product knowledge, offering promotional offers listed on the website & offers offered by the associated third parties, regardless of your DNC or DND status.

Furthermore, third parties may use Non-Personal Information in order to display advertising that reflects the interests and preferences of our user community.

If You have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us on [privacy@cartrade.com](mailto:privacy@cartrade.com).
